Resume.



Elsa Eriksson

ľ

076-767 37 05

 \bowtie

Elsa.Eriksson@medieinstitutet.se



Sköntorpsvägen 27, Stockholm



ElsaEriksson



Elsa Eriksson



http://localhost:5173/Projects

ABOUT ME

My name is Elsa, and I'm a 28-year-old female student at Medieinstitutet studying web development with specialized skills in e-commerce, and I am currently seeking an internship opportunity in this field. My training covers both frontend and backend development, with a focus on backend, that blends creativity with problem-solving. Additionally, my background in Information Design has provided me with an understanding of user experience principles. I want to refine my skills by combining this understanding with technical proficiency to learn and create user-friendly digital experiences.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

JavaScript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Sass, SQL, PHP

Libraries & Frameworks

React, Node.js

Tools & Platforms

Visual Studio Code, Git, GitHub, MySQL, Cypress, MongoDB, WordPress, WooCommerce, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Indesign, Figma, Miro

LANGUAGE

- Swedish, native
- English, good knowledge of speech, writing and reading comprehension

INTERESTS

I enjoy music exploration, discovering new artists, and experiencing live concerts. I also love to read.

REFERENCE

References available upon request

EDUCATION

2023 - Current

Web Development - E-commerce, Medieinstitutet

Studying frontend and backend development, and expect to gain proficiency in e-commerce. This includes development for e-commerce platforms as well as system support and integration with third-party systems.

2018 - 2021

Information Design - Spatial Design, Mälardalens University Developed designs based on understanding how individuals interpret and experience their surroundings, utilizing various project methodologies.

2011 - 2014

Social Science Programme, Carlforsska Gymnasium

Specialized in Humanistic and Social Sciences with an international focus, including exchanges and study trips.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022/02 - 2023/03

Barista, Thelins Konditori

I balanced proactive task management, attention to detail, and customer service.

2021/06 - 2021/12

Restaurant Assistant, Surahammars Golf Restaurant

Managed dishwashing, checkout, and maintained restaurant cleanliness with attentive service.

2018/04 - 2018/08

Receptionist, Surahammars Golf Club

Managed reception, checkout, and cleaning responsibilities to provide a welcoming environment.

2016/05 - 2016/08

Mashine Operator, Uponor AB

As a machine operator, my main tasks involved operating and monitoring machines for efficient pipe manufacturing.